hello I just I forgot that the first
time YouTube counts down it's for her
thumbnails I'm like in the thumbnail
that's for usual that feels like home so
it happens when I upload my own video
YouTube sitting here with my not the
greatest coffee that I've gotten used to
it's free so it's awesome not free it's
cheap but so you here are trying to
write out there's this piece that I need
to kind of explain that isn't the
technical like how we actually saved the
world and how we come together and do it
but it's a fundamental piece which is
the like the personal side I don't know
still a journey I'm on it's not like you
arrived and you're like I love everybody
all the time but the more I love myself
the more I love everyone else around me
and the more I love myself and everyone
like the more I'm my authentic self like
the more I dig deeper and I cover that
the more I'm capable of loving myself
it's like a new thing to love like Oh
meeting someone new or reading that like
new piece of someone someone old and
probably more like that you knows I have
know myself for as long as I'm alive
maybe even longer
who knows
and figuring out what that I don't even
know but it's like I can love that I
don't know what I'm saying
I can totally love that because I know
that my brain and that's that's one of
the pieces I am having a little bit is
Blake the reason I can love my past and
my negative side and all of that is
because I figured out what I put here on
earth to do and doing that is its own
reward whether or not I'm ever paid for
it to some degree whether or not it ever
actually comes to fruition in the real
world as long as it's still a hope for
me and as long as I'm still moving
towards making that a reality there is
so much individual blessing for me that
are not like there's the more authentic
I am the more I'm like oh I don't really
actually care if other people like me
for me like I don't if you dislike me
and I'm being me I don't care this isn't
weird thing and I'm just getting this
now so I um given ami the hope that I
cheat at board games I am like fully
just like by the way I cheated board
games which is ridiculous I enjoy
playing board games and I also enjoy
cheating at them but it's ridiculous
because if I win I cheated and if I lost
I cheated and still wants so it's like
there isn't actually a um enjoyment
there number one pointed that was Oh
being like trying to be something so
that a partner more like you so business
partners romantic partners anyone else
will like you takes away from who you
truly are and when you're taking then
then like even if they like you they're
not liking you like that's not that's
not a win
and if they dislike you
well then you're it for nothing like
it's like you lost and you cheated and I
don't think it's it's cheating I think
we're all doing the best that we that we
can with what we are currently know and
are capable of
but to figure out who you are is
something it's like you stopped caring
what the rest of the world thinks and
simultaneously the rest of the world
falls in love with you more like him in
and it's not like they'd actually do
like your perception of it changes if
you're like oh I don't I don't know like
I know when I don't like someone it's
not generally about them there are a few
big exceptions like media personalities
that I think our session politician he's
better I don't know I don't know if it's
about me but I don't like them I think
it's about the fact that destroying the
planet and I'm here too that's a little
above me I am here to say bad so you
know there's that my mom but I do love
and then it broke and I flew back
together and I don't know if I love it
more or less I don't I mean it's a
coffee mug handle it's a little less fun
to hold on to it but at the same time I
like fixing things like secondhand
things I like finding items and that's
not like other people don't have to like
that I'm not I'm like everyone has to
show the second-hand store I said but
all we have to do it like all the
clothes you have enough to be found
maybe I don't like not all my clothes
are my favorite pieces of clothing or
found like literally on the street like
I'm like oh look at that I like that and
because I like it I enjoy I enjoy it I
enjoy my stuff having like a story how
it came to be even if I don't remember
the story it's like Kent
it's that like the more the more we
embrace our true individual selves the
less in competition we are with one
another
ironically we're all trying to be this
uber version of I don't know what
society says like beautiful and smart
and courageous and know a little about
and all of those things also have a very
narrow definition like smart is like IQ
smart and beautiful is like symmetrical
face follow your gender definitely a
size zero like all the way all the way
down it's like oh no that's not that's
not beauty that's conformity that's I
mean the symmetrical face is little less
nonconformity and just like in genetics
and circumstances gestation but not in
conflict once for ourselves there is no
other you so you can't be in competition
with anyone else also who does the
saying it was both like we're we're
we're trying to get to the same
destination like we're trying to be the
super version of ourselves and therefore
not being ourselves the strange part is
when we are actually ourselves like
women are authentic selves messy
beautiful and broke in all at the same
time like all of it you accept the
broken pieces they become less broken
and that where they don't that's fine
like it's like I don't know my house is
still a mess but everyone said well it's
not it's more clean than it was because
it's like I don't have that like
constant
oh it's messy I do so that's yeah I do
something about it it's like yeah you
you can't so accept it or do something
about it
not in between and so then the more like
if there is an uber version of a human
that we are supposed to be letting go of
it helps you achieve it and the irony is
like you do have to truly let go of it
like I'm not trying to be an uber human
I'm trying to be an uber me which means
that I get to define what what it is
right like like okay so we're all gonna
like run marathons
Jozef companies and like rate is
perfectly healthy happy children and
it's like okay another that's not even
desirable to everyone why would we want
that to be achievable why everyone it's
like no what do I want to be I want to
be able to work in smoke in small groups
big groups one-on-one with people to
create solutions in the world and work
through a process together and see
things come to fruition that we've
created so I'm creating the system to do
that because the system doesn't exist
and I can see how if that system did
exist not just for me but for everyone
to be able to do it not I get together
with six of my friends and decide that
we're gonna like write this app then
this computer corporation even if we did
it for the world even if it was purely
social enterprise purely nonprofit there
would still be one way to convince
people of that that which is layers but
um it isn't the same like it's like it
has to be available for everyone
everyone not you've reached your uber
Hut itself and now you're you're allowed
to have people and a Colleen and a team
like know if that caught like whatever
and that's that when it's an internal
drive when it's like oh what brings me
happiness what and I still live in a
broken world and I'm still broken like I
still like my anxiety it's the best of
me and I yell at my kid and I'm like
impatient and I'm like the more I
embrace that trauma the more I become
that and I don't like that piece of it
but also the less I become that because
it's like I don't sit in that like I
can't apologize for it I'm like oh I
have tantrum but I'm like just have
tantrums kids know what they're doing
look it's like and I'm not a tantrum
like I'm the opposite of that it like
I'm bitter name they don't freak out on
people very often I freak out about
people but not on people they'll freak
out about something that that's going on
in the world but I'm not like calling
them trumping knowing I'm right like
I'll freak out about like the state of
the world but not like my friends or how
people gossip and not of like to my
friend that they've been gossiping right
like it's not like you're a gossip it's
like why don't gossip you don't like
that sort of thing
and so I don't know like the times I
have freaked out like I freaked out on
my sister a few months ago when she came
to visit which I wasn't like happy about
it was like a mat but I was at the same
time I was like no that was processing
like I was supposed to happen I still
apologize for freaking out and I still
you know like the stuff that happened I
apologized for but not and there's of
course I couldn't hit her I didn't you
know say anything horribly horribly mean
just freaked out I just had a tantrum
and it was truth behind it and like
getting to that truth was part of it
like oh no there's there's a piece here
that's with it like isn't coming out
like terrible not gonna tantrum and
that's the feeds they're good we did
steal with you still haven't quite dealt
with but we remember Benchley well so
our person honors that person me I just
went up to one person that happened hi
person I also feel like there's a lot of
robots on I was on your periscope last
night and when you type in something
someone else jumps on and types in like
the exact same thing and I kept tapping
on repeat they computer copying you and
like I don't know it was weird I have to
go on and she's search with what that
actually was that I have like seven
subscribers so like a wading birds start
getting to the point where people jump
off but that if I like call people out
every time they might called that's
hopefully calling people in but um
anyway yeah this idea that we're
supposed to be perfect versions of
ourselves is broken I and I it's very
broken for me I don't know how broken it
is for everyone else because that's a
piece of the broken - but like we find a
solution for ourselves like this won't
work for everybody no won't it will not
work for everybody you're gonna offer it
cuz it will work for some people like
the Tony Robbins and then where it's
like if you do that it will work it's
like that's not first of all that in
itself that statement is very
problematic like if you do it it will
work well some people are came to look
doing it like that's a big piece that's
and it will work it's another because
there's tons of people who do I I tried
the Tony Robbins way and it doesn't work
for me it's like doing the actual work
there's pieces about that work and the
party sis event that I'm like no it
doesn't feel
like I can go and learn how to put
makeup on probably capable of that but
when I went and gotten my makeup done in
like a department store and I haven't
done it for probably like two decades at
least um maybe not quite that long no
make me a high school student um that
like it was it wasn't that I didn't look
good and said I didn't feel like me I'm
like this is a nice face but online and
that's what I feel like about all of it
like it's like even if it even if it is
good it's not me like it needs to be me
authentic and I'm like losing my train
of thought getting my coffee and it's
been over ten minutes so I'm gonna go
and cut I got to be able to jump on and
do this even though it's a Sunday and
I'm not doing this on Sundays but my kid
is strangely still sleeping not so
strange goes to bed like sleep by 9:30
which was also strange because it's
summer I'm gonna be the earliest she'd
slept a long time anyway have a good day
and I will see people if anyone's
watching this on Monday